Hello Priya Jewellers, are you also
worried about your valuables like
loss, theft, robbery, solution to all these?
I, Akshay Kothari from Ambika Insurance, we
specialize in insurance or business
insurance. We are
insuring around 700 jewellers today
and we have more than 1000 clients.
So today we will give you a
complete explanation of Jewellers Insurance on
all these topics like
what is insured in your shop, transit
means if you are taking your employee or artisan for the
purpose of jewellery, then
how do you insure him and your
exhibition, your logistics insurance like
if you have to hire a logistics provider or professional
logistics, then there
is cash insurance or if you face
any kind of fraud, then its
insurance. Many things will be discussed today,
but our assurance is that you will get
Jewellers Insurance in full detail.
We will explain the area/region, this will
definitely make you confident that you are
a Jeweller.  How can you take insurance,
what are its criteria and in this
we will also explain to you how the pricing is calculated for
Jewellers Insurance,
so what will happen from this, whether you
take insurance from us or from any other
advisor, at least you should know
what is available in the market today and
how insurance works and
simply we do not have expertise only in sales,
we also have experience in service,
so if you have any
doubts on this product or
you feel that we have to
give consultancy at your doorstep, then simply call on
this number, we will come and
give consultation for free and our only importance is that just
like we do door step sales, we
also provide door step clean, today we will
make you such an expert that you
cannot just buy Jewellers Insurance but
can also send it to someone else, so let us move ahead and
learn about Jewellers Insurance,
but in my case, this is my request, there is a
small rule that you sit in a secluded place
or sit with us for 40 minutes.
Dedicate yourself to the people, take your tea, coffee, snacks, whatever you
need and comfortably
login with headphones and take as much knowledge as possible
so that if you have any worry, if you do
not understand anything, then you can easily contact us
tomorrow and you know us
because our up and all this happens a lot
in the market, so you will get our details there also, so let's
move ahead to jewelers,
so my Priya Jewellers, today we understand for
whom insurance is not made, those to whom
we do not want to sell or
those who do not need to take insurance,
we meet many jewelers and there is a certain
category of people who say
that we have been doing business for 20 years, we have been doing
business for many years,
we have not faced any problem till date, so there will be no
problem in the future also,
no, insurance is an discipline, it will
not happen to you, date is very secondary or
yours will be almost very strong, but
what about your employees, your next
generation is going to come in the business  I don't
know if they are as strong as you or not, or if they are not as smart as you, I do
n't know, so anything can happen at some
moment of time and no one can guarantee that.
In today's date, secondly,
people who don't have GST registration,
who open their own business and you are not
compliant with the government, they cannot get
insurance because when
we have to give a claim, you have a bill, what is the
claim bill, how much amount do you have to take, if there is no
GST on insurance then the next day
your bill will not be accepted. There is
no need to do marketing or to
expand the business by purchasing goods of different designs from another democracy or another state or another city,
or I don't need to participate in new exhibitions,
I just have to
stick to my traditional method, so
insurance is not made for them also.
People and lots of people, we see
that they do not need shop insurance
because they say that they have
kept their shop only for time pass,
those customers  They don't entertain anyone much
and brother-in-law is not very serious about the jewellery
business because other businesses are giving them a lot of
profit and a lot of use, so
for those people also there is no jewellers insurance,
we have not come up with this thing yet,
listen to the rumours, some people in the market say
that we paid the
insurance premium of life
insurance in cash and the
party ran away with it, so here you do
n't have to make any cash payment, in insurance, insurance is
between you and the company with me being
your advisor with me being your
advisor and your lis alright, so in this you do
n't have to trust anyone and give cash in hand and even after talking to people about this, they say that in our hall marking, some other party ran away with half a gram or a full gram, so what about them, they themselves don't trust many people, so
see, if you judge the entire industry by looking at one or two people, then
you can never judge
anyone, there is trust everywhere, there is
risk involved with the businessman everywhere, everywhere  A
businessman has to move ahead by trusting
because only then he becomes a big businessman. All
they care about is that if you say let's
start a jewellery shop, then you will
say the price is too high, let's invest the
money in the stock market, it falls, oh let's do
railway stations, oh
no, everyone in it is a thief, they run away with the money, they do
n't get land, so people who do
n't know how to invest money, people who don't know how to spend money on
their
security, there is
no jeweler's insurance for them and it is simple, people who ca
n't spend, they can't
work, so come
our dear, let's understand for
whom we made insurance and
who should take insurance, these are those who are
very serious about their business, who
think that if I do my business with great
passion, if I have a business, then
I can earn this much, I can achieve these goals well
and those who
are very serious about their career, who know that if I work
hard, I put my money in, with so much
trouble, I put my bandwala to do my
business, the jewellery business is such a
business that gives you capital  It is
available on appreciation and profits are also available on Roshan,
so we always consider this as one of the
most earning businesses, those whose
insurance we have been doing for the last five years,
we have easily seen that their stock has doubled, so
such an easy and such a good business is not there on the story as
well and secondly,
we see people in this category who are a little reserved,
we jewellers are a little reserved, a little daring, a
little polished people, so we always
think that they are very worried that if there is no
charge, they come to the shop quietly, observe for 5 minutes and go away, then
we get tensed that
what did he observe after coming for 10-15 minutes, 1/2
hour, if someone is standing outside and watching our shop, then
sometimes we feel that he is
planning and plotting something, so
many jewellers remain sleepless about this
that what is going to happen next, so it is
not in your control, someone will come and steal,
someone will come and rob, someone will come and take away the goods,
you do not have to do anything, you
just have to do it because date is  You have to transfer all these uncontrollable
things to your insurance company.
Many people are confused about
security measures, do
they have to keep a watchman outside the shop,
do we have to
keep a burglar or an alarm, do we have to make an
open purchase and keep it in the office. So, they are very confused
about security
measures, what should we keep, what should we not
keep. I have seen many people who
take insurance from the bank,
take insurance from logistics companies. Now the
performance of the bankers and logistics companies is
in supplying your goods or the
bankers'
in giving you financial assistance, they have very little knowledge of insurance
and their product tax
price is very cheap which you are not able to understand and
you end up taking advice from
different players at a very high cost and
not getting good service, so what happens with this is
you keeping your insurance three times.
We have such clients
who take insurance from us, from the bank,
from the logistics company for insurance,
which has no significance.
Many times our policy gets rejected at one place without you knowing the reasons
being  The wordings will be different or the
list interest that will be settled for your claim the day after tomorrow.
Many times,
insurance helps you a lot if you have to take a bank loan.
Or if you are traveling with precious metals for your business,
we have discussed this
many times in our organization meetings that
if you are
traveling with precious metals for business, be it
over India for marketing, purchasing, supply,
any reason, exhibition, then we highly
recommend that you have insurance.
So basically, those people who are not covered under insurance in the last slide, we
recommend that you
take insurance. So, people from all these categories
who can or
want to take insurance,
we have created our Pro Jewellers Insurance based on
our experience
in the industry for so many years. According to that, these are small
company papers, extra company
outer company papers, extra papers
which we face
less in logistics or exhibitions or we
delegate less to any third party.  So, after doing
research on selected jewellers, right from the big ones to the medium ones to the small ones, they have put all the
conditions which are made easy at the time of a claim by
agreeing to something with the insurance company and
agreeing to something with the jeweller, so that your claim becomes easy.
See, let's come and you have to understand that the game
of insurance is a
game, so right now, on the
game of roulette, when we know what are the rules,
like if we enter on numbers, then we
get 36 times, if we enter on red, then we
get input device, if we enter on black, so
you have to know what are these rules, so
if we polish these rules a little and make them easy, then
this insurance can be more effective.
And according to the
statistics we used to talk about in this, the
company settled about
99.64% of the rates, so all of you who are
registered with us, you will
get links to IBI, IBPS, nothing but
Insurance Broker of India, so you can
go and it is in  Employment of IRDA
IRDA is a regulatory body like
SEBI is the regulatory body in your share market,
similarly in insurance IRDA is a
regulatory body which drafts the terms and rules for everyone,
so according to them,
you can see the statistics of what kind of claims have been made in which company, you
can enjoy the insurance,
okay so in our today's session, what are the
benefits that you will get from this, so
in this thing we will make you jewellers smart
jewellers, so what does jeweller mean, you have taken
bond with your story, opened
your shop, made a showroom or
started any business, be it wholesale business or manufacturing business,
and from here you are doing sales as well and slowly and gradually
and gradually the
income is generating, okay now from here you have to become,
which after all this is done, okay, which is
sitting at one place and controls the growth,
you do not interfere in every department,
like your sales
department will be purchase  Once the department is formed, then the
owner will not have to maintain all these small inter-office departments all the time
and
if the procedure of this insurance is
followed correctly, then a systematic
formation is formed and what happens with it is that you can
open 100 new branches, you
can open 10 branches, you can open a thousand branches
or you can free yourself by sitting at one place and
maintaining your single business cleanly,
so our point is that
you have invested, now build it
and make it a legacy and this is your
most important thing because jailer's business is
such a business where whatever you sell, whatever you
earn, you
invest it back in stock and increase the stock of your shop, so let's
come to our first learning or
first coverage, which we call it, that is, the
thing from which this insurance will protect us,
we
call it in simple language natural
calamities or incidents caused by nature or for
which there was no reason and the incident happened to him,
then consider this  Like if you get lost today due to
lightning, earthquake,
storm or getting washed away by water
like tsunami
and all these things, then
we provide you protection from natural calamities from such reasons.
Now, there is a lot of
difference in this, like if you get lost due to a short,
if
suppose the explosion happened due to a bomb or due to
bursting outside, then there
is relief by taking all these information. What does close of proximity
mean, which is the first and
primary reason, then it is close of proximity. For
example, if a truck driver causes an
accident with a person, but in this the
truck driver was actually losing control
and was
trying to save the person who was riding a bicycle, but close of
proximity is what should be called an accident, then
you should get an insurance claim and to
insure it, we have given
an additional coverage by making an accidental damage in it.
This simple meaning of accidental damage is
that if there is a
building nearby whose
building is underground
Our jewellery got buried in which
ok so after every slide or every
explanation we have kept some effective in which we frequently ask
questions so that
whatever doubts you generally have
after explaining some coverage,
we have explained them clearly in this, it is 100%
you will have more doubts than this, that is why we have given
our number below, you
can message your questions and we will
happily answer your questions tomorrow without any cost way bill
ok so now as per the last light it was
asked in this that can we select which was parallel bill like
means can we select some parallel
like if I want only today and storm
and hurricane or I want only earthquake and
accident damage then can we select
no, you do not need to select this because
we give you everything inbuilt in the
policy and
charge you the premium only once ok in
books of account or last during
Sachin incident which are our books,
our computers are like this  When there is a
natural disaster and there is a loss, then
we recommend you to
make a backup in your pen drive and
keep it at your home or whatever happens to you,
you should add a paper to your cloud account
or if your books get destroyed
then in that case
we can get it proved from your last ITR
so they have four to five
parameters where one when your pen comes we
will help you and they will bill note it but the rejection on IT is
now the human calamities
that we see in our today's date have increased a lot
like a customer comes
and tries to see the items by behaving like a customer
and during that time either he
changes the item or he goes away with an item in his pocket
or when we are
displaying the item then
three to four people come and someone runs away with
our item from behind without our permission
or when we close the office
then someone enters inside for four to five days and
breaks the office and steals it and goes away, then
we take action against him  It is called buggery or when we are
sitting in the office for four-five days and there is a
strike without any reason, in that our
shop is broken or our goods are taken away by threatening us, then
we call it,
we have done it in two parts, one which happens
in your premises, so what do we
call 'my premises', when it either happens in your shop, at the
shop of the logistics person or
at the shop of your artisan or when
you are travelling with your employee and
during the travel you have to stay, that is, in a
hotel room or at any of your houses, then also
this human climax, wherever the goods are stored, that is, in
any house, shop
or at the vault of logistics, when the goods are constantly stored,
then we do all these
parallel analysis of it, like shopping,
test, buggery, decorative etc.,
we understand some of the frequently asked questions about these,
okay, so in this we get a lot of questions
in this area where there is theft, robbery
or coming to the shop and taking away the goods, okay, so
in this we understand that
jewellers ask this question a lot of time, now
if  Someone else's goods are lying in our shop,
like it is your wholesaler's goods
or some other shopkeeper's goods or
suppose it is not a customer, you had kept your
ring or someone's jewels
in your shop for polishing or repairing, then at that time if any
kind of incident happens like human
climate or natural calamities, then it is taxed, yes
hundred percent you have to take
an extension which we
call stock head in trust and
commission brother also jeweler, so when you
take this extension in your insurance, then
all this is also taxed,
we give this in writing in our NDA policy,
next comes when it gets stolen, then
how will you prove that this was the
weight of the product and you have to set this much amount,
we can say more or we
can say less, so in this it is very simple, we
suggest you only one thing, if your
product is by bifurcation, then
this is the weight of a specific product and this is
its valuation, you can record
it as closing stock in your books.  I understand that we should
maintain a stock ledger or a stock record in
which it is known that all these items were
weighed. So what happens with that is that the
next day you weigh them when you
put them in the store and at night when you
put them in the store and when
you take them out in the morning, if there is a difference in
your weight then they will bill you for something, so according to that
we will
understand what is the next procedure by looking at your CCTV. So what are the security
measures required? People say that
if we have to take this insurance then
what security measures do we have to take?
Right now there are many insurances
which say that you should keep an armed watchman, you should keep a
burglar or an alarm, you should keep a regular watchman, you should
buy a gunner, so what happens is that
sometimes they are efficient, sometimes they are not efficient,
sometimes we are able to handle them, sometimes we do not, so by
sidelining all this we give
you insurance without any other fear, telling that
you just have a CCTV camera
which is mandatory.  By applying this, your savings will
run in seconds and most importantly,
keep your stock, especially gold, diamond and other precious metals apart from silver, in a safe
after the business is over at night. Then, when you leave the office, take
all your keys,
emergency exit keys and safe
keys with you and go home.
We know that maintaining a stock wise summary is a difficult task
for jewellers.
Sometimes our
purchase bills come in lots and their sales also happen in lots. So,
you don't need to worry about all these things.
When you are ready to buy insurance,
we give you an understandable
format. You have to make a few changes. Because when
you want insurance, it is like an insurance. There will be
terms and conditions. You have to follow them a little and you have to
follow the company. So, what
is the weekend insurance? There is a certain point of
investigation where we can prove your loss and get
you a pre-claim easily.
Sometimes, there are part human calamities caused by
violent transit, meaning humans, which happen to
our employees.  Be it our marketing
heads or purchase heads or the
owners themselves or these logistics people who are going to
meet the wife or our workers
who are taking the goods from their shop to their
shop or
to a third party for billing, heating, refreshing
or for polishing for some work, so
what is transit involved in this, the
simple meaning of translation is that whenever any
goods go out of the office for any business purpose, what can happen to it, only
two things can happen to it,
one is either some person can threaten you and
take away the bag or that person
can snatch the bag from you by putting a hole in it and hitting it and take it away, so
such things happen
in translation which we call robbery and hold
up, now the simple meaning of robbery is that
someone snatched it from your hand, the simple meaning of holder is that
someone took it from you by threatening, so
this can happen to anyone, be it you, your
employees, your artisans, your
hallmarking people, your  If we are transit
logistics people, then
for their protection also this transit parallel
comes to us, okay okay,
so now a lot of questions
come from people about how we can transport  Let's do it,
ok, so step by step frequently the
last question is what is the RD
document required while travelling, so
you carry this document when you travel,
either your travel voucher which
we call return [ __ ] delivery challan, whenever
you are taking it for marketing,
going for a show or for an
exhibition, then
whenever you travel, write a challan on
which you will mention what work you are doing,
what action you are taking, its format will be shared with
you, when you take the policy then you do
not have to format it, but it is
similar, if whatever words are taken in it, if
all that is entered in your format then it is done,
secondly, carry the first page of the insurance copy
with you whenever you
travel because if you have any office or
any post,
we also have insurance, we are very
intelligent jewellers and we are travelling for this purpose,
secondly the question comes that should they have
CCTV camera, this is not while travelling, obviously,
obviously  It is not possible,
what is it, you can get first and last evidence
like if there is a CCTV camera of when our employee took this bag or
we left the office, then it is
understood that
yes, it was taken for this purpose, secondly, your
dispute is relief for which we also have interest, okay, the
simple meaning of interest is that
you have to write on it for what purpose you are
taking it, whether it is return
[ __ ] delivery voucher, whether it is given to the artisan, then it is
issue voucher, whether it is
given to another shopkeeper, then it is
approval voucher, okay, if it is
given to a worker, not for reduction, when it is given to a worker
for reduction, then it is
voucher, okay, and on an order, then you should write it as a
wiper kit, write the name of the person to whom you are giving it,
write his name on top, for what
purpose are you giving it, then it is given here, then
we understand that the
goods were going out for this purpose which was business purpose,
and outside  If it has been done then
CCTV camera must be there only.
Okay so the next question comes where should it be
filed and then during an FIR in
travel. Any affair is a little bit less nowadays
after the norms are a little free, the zero which happens
then you can file it on the story also but
where do you have to file an FIR,
generally we
call it the place of incident where the
loss has happened or where the crime has happened,
so the date should be the reporting place. FIR can be filed at that place.
Many times I get this question
that we are carrying goods and we fall
asleep or then we get robbed.
See one thing keep in mind that you should not lose your gold or
your goods by keeping them with you. This
is an avoidance for the policy or it
is a negligence. After taking the policy, we
always suggest that if you ever
travel with goods, then
travel on two journeys. If sleeping is
required then one journey should sleep, one journey should take
care of the goods and the other  If one goes then the
other can take care of the goods,
so you don't have to sleep like this when you are carrying the goods, whether it's the
bag in the truck or the
truck, in simple words people say I am going by bus, I am
going by train, so I keep the
goods in the trunk, if I am
going by flight, then I give the goods in check-in baggage,
so you don't have to do all that,
when we say insurance in travelling in
transit, in custody means in the custody of owner,
employee, whoever it is,
logistics person, transport person, artisan person,
in custody means you should stay within one hand's yard,
Malkabi also, so what is the use of that,
you can only be a robbery and a hold up
when you are within one hand's yard and
that is covered relief in insurance, okay can I take this
policy in the public
transport
when I am travelling with the
material, so its sample means that yes
you can use any transport, bus,
train, flight, whatever you like, just the bag should be
in your custody,
we should keep this in mind and
you will have more questions people
These are hundred percent of the common questions that we are asked
and your questions can be taken on the
number there and you can message me comfortably or
you can message us tomorrow at some other time, then we
can explain the DP a little more to you.
Next comes your Jewellers Insurance.
A summary of what we have discussed till now, so
basically there are two things in Jewellers Insurance,
Premises and Transit
Premises, that is your shop, your
branches, your house, okay or when
you make an employee travel, then your hotel room,
when there is a worker's place, there are logistics
vaults, there are exhibition stalls, so that
means wherever there is a place where metal will be
stored, we call it Premises Bullet, so what will
we do in this, so
whatever natural and human climate there is,
we have summarized it, which your shop
lifting has been tested,
from today if any natural incident happens then
all this is coming and taking your natural and human calamities
outside, someone from your family is
taking them outside, okay in this you have to take
care of the employee or family member  You
can take it out only for business purposes, not for wearing it to a wedding
and if something happens there, it will
not be covered. If you are carrying your goods
for business purposes for marketing,
purchasing, issuing, displaying,
then also its coverage is available.
Next comes when workers, logistics
workers, we often see that when
workers come from your shop and take goods to their shop, then
transit is happening here also,
logistics workers come to your shop, take the
goods, load them in their truck, their
truck goes from your shop,
loads them in the truck,
takes them back to their vault, and
from their vault, the next day, whenever it is
your flight time or you have to travel on road, then you take
out your van and take it back. You
see, you have to travel a lot with
IT, even then
we provide you
this insurance in
which your
natural and human climate is covered.
Now
after you understand all this, IT is very
simple,
which I will tell you in the next, but
in very simple, you will get all this insurance.
When you are affected by any third party or any outsider, it is
also by nature
and by human, till now we have explained that to you,
we have done it for you, now
what are the necessary conditions to follow in this, firstly keep
your CCTV camera on, recording 24×
7, we see some people
who go out of the shop at night and turn off the
CCTV, please do not do that, keep
your CCTV with recording on,
you should account for 80% to 90% of the stock daily, maintain it clearly,
how many pieces were there, how many pieces were there,
how many pieces were there, keep it in a ledger, it
is not mandatory for silver jewellers because silver jewellery
cannot go inside the set, okay so for daily stock
taking and maintenance of gold, platinum
and diamond, you will have to take daily stock in the
morning while opening and turning in the night, then
you will know what is the stock,
what has been sold, how much is there or if something is missing,
then its next procedure is
how do we recover it from insurance, okay
like your KYC blue, in this basically it is simply that the
movie and  Customer no. Your
employee no. Your worker, okay, so whoever
you give goods to for any work, then keep
his Aadhar, PAN photo, if there is any certificate like
GST, if we have to, then
you must keep his Aadhar photo and
PAN, so from this we come to
know that if someone runs away, then
how can we get his identity,
keep his joining letter also with his description, for
which date, on which
date he joined,
what is his description, what all work will he do, okay, so
keep all this and
next, keep an authorization letter, what does it
mean, many times your
third parties, like workers,
smiths, manufacturers, okay,
logistics people, then you should prepare an
authorization letter for them that these people have to
collect the goods and we will deliver it to them, because
many times it happens
that the owner does not come and his servants come
and then the owner says that no, I did
not even tell you to give the goods to him.
Why did you give it for this, then you should make an authorization letter,
whichever employee of the owner comes to
your shop to take your goods, so
what happens with this is your safety and your
procedure that you have given the goods to them,
so now you must have heard this everywhere,
now you should know
what is pro insurance, why is pro insurance bad,
okay, so have we
changed the wording in this, okay, so what happens when a
contract becomes stronger,
so basically pro insurance means
your interests,
interest means when your order is placed
or
sales order or travelling order
or when your order is placed or any order is placed, then
during this a slip is made,
interest minute, means we are
giving the goods to someone by trusting him, who will
return it to us after earning our money, so during this
what do you tell the other company that your interest should
come in serial number, it should be
prepared in duplicate and
you have to maintain it one by one cleanly here also
and your evidence has to be kept at some other place
also  So what
happens with this? Many times we see that when the serial
number and duplicate of any item are prepared, then
when a claim comes in, sometimes it happens that the
purchase department gave a different number, the shield
department gave a different number, we gave a different number from home,
when we were
taking it for overnight storage and the
next day for work, then it was with a different number, so what is there in this,
many
problems arise due to which at the time of claim we
see in interest that the
claim is rejected, the family
and the workers are safe,
what do they say in other insurances,
but when we look at diamond dealers, when we
look at big silver manufacturers, what happens, it is not like this,
you store the articles inside the safe,
okay, so what extension do we give
you in this, can you keep it in a steel cupboard, can you keep it
in a cupboard, can you
keep it in a locked drawer, wherever possible,
meaning if you had the facility to
keep this item properly and lock it, then you
can keep it, otherwise you
You can leave that out and go with your shooter band.
You had seen all these coverages, human and
natural calamities together, along with this
we have also given you accidental damage, meaning
you have losses from any other reason on
jewellery, then the bill will be covered by us out of the
limit as per your requirement, like
we give 100% payment to the silversmith who has a
complete silver business, to the rest we
give 10 to 15 percent,
okay and exhibition, all
exhibitions are covered here, you will
get a different price for such signature, for that you have to
take your policy from some other place or we will
not give it to you and if you have to do a
private exhibition then you cannot do it,
if you have to do a photoshoot then you should
not do it, so we will not write all this nonsense and useless thing
in your insurance, so
you should be absolutely sure and
participate in all the exhibitions, build your strong base, make
your name big and small everywhere, I
mean, it comes to employees,
what happens in other policies,
like they think that all the employees
come  There should be a salary for them, those who
work or those who are family members to
whom we do not give remuneration, then they do
not come and take other insurance in it,
so what is very simple in ours,
whatever your contractual is, it is non-remunerated, then
all of that gets taken under it and
we have put such a wording in it that
you get very fast claims, okay because
this wording is very easy, you can understand this wording, so it is
not that you and I will
not get the claim from that insurance, in
fact those who are going to take insurance from us have received the
claim in 15-20 days
and one important reason for this is that we have
made the wordings very easy, tomorrow
we do not even need to do any setting on the story
with the insurance company and we give it to you after doing a very
profile, so
what all does our Pro Insurance do for you, like we
go on a tour package where there are
train tickets and hotel stay there and then
taxi, we do sightseeing there and the
entry charges there, if  If you have to
go to any place, then all that should be included in a single package,
like we have made this Pro
Insurance, in this we have
put different sections in which your risk tax is done,
which is area one, whatever
your valuables are in those premises, that is,
whatever you have kept in your shop
or at your branches, okay, second
comes valuable in travel by owner and
employees, that is, you are your employees,
you are going to travel with this goods on the story also,
if there is going to be a tax with travel, then that is a tax
in this area,
which you pay less according to jewellery,
you pay less according to the jewellery sector,
for doing anything, then it gets
covered in this area, they also have
both tax and transit tax, then the
area of ​​valuable in custody of logistics players, that is, whatever your
valuables like BB, Sequel,
Malka, Brings, through this you
send the story or order it from the story also, then the tax for
it will be  It will be in their
vault and the transit will happen, that is, with
their love and yours, Gan Maa's Gan Maa will
come and take it to the vehicle, from the vehicle it will be
taken back to the vault, from the vault it will be
unloaded back to the vehicle and will
take it to the airport, so in this process
both stereo transit taxes are involved,
in area 5 there are taxes in your valuable exhibition,
you
can participate in any exhibition, then
we do the deposit and transit tax for that too, then
further your money insurance means whatever is the amount of money,
whether it is your cash collection,
cash deposit, whether it is in the bank or
in cash premiums, then we do that tax in this area
and then the non-fidelity area
which is a relief to many people is the fidelity
guarantee of employees and third party
fidelity or infidelity, it means
that if someone betrays your trust
or cheats you, then we do that tax
in this area, in this area we do
a little typing for the jewelers, so for this
you will have to contact us once and get
its certificate from us.
I want you to understand that
whatever areas we have seen now, we have been
affected by outside or some third party, like for example we are
roaming with our wallet and when someone snatches our money from behind, then it is an
external source which
we do not know about, so
what happens in Fidelity, it is that they have an interested party, we have
given our goods to someone to earn some money,
like our employee, we have
marketing purchasing, our third
party, like we have killed a hallmarker
or given goods to a craftsman or
any logistics player and
they run away with it, then it happens
separately in Fidelity area, well
as we had promised you that
after the explanation of our insurance, you can also find out its pricing yourself, if you
want it yourself then our
insurance agent, bank, you know you can always do
business with you, you yourself,
insurance broker, our insurance broker,
they are very, you take your money,
channel partner, okay, so what happens in this,
they have design dispro insurance,
whatever insurance you have  Is it about travelling for example premises have been done,
transit risk has been done,
okay exhibition tax, is it about
your money, so for this we have
made a risk policy, right now in the risk policy
we have mixed five other policies and made a
certain full policy,
we have to tell how much stock is there,
you are in zone one, you are an employee, okay, you are an
owner, now you are travelling on the story also,
but for the purpose of purchasing, marketing
sales,
this insurance comes in zone 2,
zone 3, whichever third
party you issue goods to, be it a worker,
goldsmith, hall marker, to them
for making your jewellery,
then your entire tax is done in zone three, okay
with the player, okay, like BBC Koyal
brings goods, Ambe, you send it to the story also, you
ask for it from the story also, then
you can get it valued in zone four, okay, you
can get it valued during the exhibition of zone 5,
what does infidelity mean?  If you are
cheated by someone,
either by your employees
or by your Smith Hall Marking workers,
manufacturers, logistics players, then
basically when you underpay to any third party
or underpay to any employee
and he runs away with your goods, then
we cover that with fidelity insurance,
that too is available to you in our insurance and
I am not explaining it much to you right now, once
you
learn to calculate the cost and you know the
approximate price, you will get
your insurance,
okay, so basically you have to login to our website
www.ambika jewellers.com or you can
login to Ambika spot.com and do the jewellery
insurance calculator, then
you will get a get free estimate on it, as soon
as you click on it,
you will get all these sections and according to these sections,
you enter each coverage and
get your quotation comfortably, in this you keep two things in
mind, one is the coverage that you are not
taking, like some people do
not necessarily have coverage for exhibition, some people do not necessarily have coverage for cash  If it
happens then please do not leave it in black
and make it zero, if you make it zero then the
calculator
will multiply zero by zero, if it remains in black then it will
not be able to multiply, so as it
multiplies you will get rates on all sides,
you will get your perfect total
calculation, okay we
reduce the minimum to 20000,
we reduce the premium below 20000 rupees but they will
get a charger, so we do not charge premium below 20000, so even if
yours is 10, 12,
15 thousand, still the minimum way bill will be
20000, okay and there are many
discounts and offers available in it, so
as you finish your calculation, okay you can
learn to do all the calculations from any of us, so
you can do it with us anytime, you
can ask any doubts, then the bill will be
ready, you explain
what we used to talk about earlier also, discipline,
so we have to do the same with discipline, see the sold way tech and
insurance, I mean  One thing is that when we have a
friend, he had
bought a shop in Ulsoor, which even today is
very sad when I talk about him,
I am not going to take his name, his
shop was 6 months old,
he had collected money from many places and had stocked it with a
stock of Rs. 1.25 crore in the shop, the
next day, as if he was
taking bribe for the entire shop, the
poor guy went into such depression, so much so that
he doesn't even talk to anyone, his
laughter, his happiness, the way
he used to come and
talk to me from a friend's night, all of that has now
reduced and when we
go into depression, only think that the chances of heart attack
increase a lot or we feel like committing suicide,
so
what happens to us because when this happens to us,
people outside start insulting us, we are
always in such a state, we are always in a slow state, we do
n't pay attention to it in any work, we don't pay attention to it, so
you children should be careful about all this
because we don't know when a person's time
comes, but a
backup.  It is very important to have a plane as well.
Okay, let's not talk about all this, it gets very
depressing. But I have
seen many jewelers not sleeping at
night. Hey, who was standing in our shop many times?
Hey, that charger,
DK, shop and then went back. What was their
importance? So get rid of all this. Invest. The
second is the
benefits. What are the benefits of insurance for you?
See, I am currently
offering 600 plus jewelers in our corps. So when you
join, your money will be reduced for those 600 people.
When they have a problem or when
you have a problem, we will help those 600 jewelers
with your problem. So what
happens is that our
network becomes strong because of this. Our industry grows.
And when we tell the insurance company that
we have such a big portfolio, then
any insurance company will be
ready to write jewelers insurance.
You can also believe it. That is why, for the last 10-12 years,
many insurance companies have
run away from jewelers insurance. Okay, the ones who are ready to
write jewelers insurance are very weak.
This is our chance that if we
give a big amount to Jewellers Insurance then the
company will never think of running away.
Second thing, sometimes in life when
we are in trouble, we need a helping hand, we need someone to
come and hold our hand and lift us up and
save us from any problem or we have
also seen that there are many small
jewellers who have taken insurance from us, then
in one or two seasons someone comes and
steals from them and their entire season gets
wasted, okay, so at that time they will get some
relief.  It is that hey, even if we did not earn much in our life, it did
not harm us, we will withdraw money from the story and get it
back and when you
take insurance, it shows your attitude,
many people due to overconfidence are
not able to teach the right meaning of life to their small children or their next generation or their employees, so when you
cannot take insurance, you
cannot secure what you have earned,
then how will they give you any other useful thing, so show
your attitude and as you take insurance,
we give you one thing, you feel
very happy from within because you
go to a temple and donate and
you invest money at one place for your own benefit, then you
get a lot of happiness in it and it is an pride, seeing you,
tomorrow your children will also learn the same thing that
our father was disciplined, whatever happened in
India at the time of insurance
and due to this, till date, whatever has happened or not happened,
that is secondary but we should also follow this
and along with all this, Ambika guarantees you one thing,
that is growth as much as you  Also
invest in your insurance. You
invest at 5:00 in the evening, you
invest at 11:00 in the morning, we
give you a guarantee by night that whatever
investment you have made, one or two customers will give
you the earnings and go away.
So after all this, it is up to
you whether you should take insurance
or not. You can
learn a lot from anyone who deals in insurance in the market.
Okay, some will be
fast, some will be slow, but then my request to you is that
you should take a good insurance and become
a good citizen and show your future
generation that insurance is very important. So, I
want to talk to you in a simple way. This is
my friend John. One day he was drowning
in the sea. You can see him. There were
5 boats around him who came to save him and said that today
John should be brought up, then he said no, no, you
people who are God will come to save me, I am
God's servant. And then the second and the third person
also said that today John, I will save you, then
he said no, no, you who are God will
save me, so doing like this, he drowned and died
and when he went up  So God
asked him, he
asked God
why didn't you save me, then God told him,
you fool, I sent five boards for you to
save you and you were looking at me, so those who have a
lot of
faith in God, then I
say that God, please
send one vote to insurance, so you should
choose wisely and in this you are off, so
this is our customer care number, our
offices are currently in Karnataka, Andhra Pradesh,
Tamil Nadu, Kerala and we provide
services across India, now you
can call on any of these numbers and
you can avail your facilities with us, ok
our customer care number is directly
my number, claim set number
973066, if you have any doubts or you
need any clarification or you want us to come to
your office and explain this entire
procedure to you, then
verify your insurance, you
can call us anytime on these numbers, you
can also take a screenshot of it,
so in our insurance, we have made
big bullion  We insured dealers
like Ambika, Infinity Bullion,
Hasti, Matashree, etc.
We have also insured big dealers
like
Vijay Gems and Raj Diamond, the biggest wholesale diamond dollar, and
we have insured these people as well. We have insured
big gold jewelers like Shriman Doma
's
Arihant, Joel Craft, and many such people.
We insured big silver
jewelry like Mahalsa Purple.
We have insured big retailers
like Shri Sai Gold Palace, Raj Diamond,
Shri Ganesh Hallmarking, Ambika
Hallmarking. We have insured them as well. There are many such
well-known names in the grading institute which I have
not been able to include yet. If you come to Kindle, please
go to our website and see, many
names of both are written there. Or
whenever we come to meet you, we always have
someone or the other
who is insured by us, so we will
connect you with them, sir.
And I thank you very much that
you had the courage to come to a training session.
Understand Jewellers Insurance and try its many
remedies, we
from Mumbai thank you very much,
we will help you, so the more you
meet us, the more you will meet me, you will keep talking,
you will understand how we do business, how it is
going, so we are also in
bullion coins, hallmarking, refinery, silver
article insurance, okay, right now we are
concentrating a lot on
insurance because it is the need of the hour and whatever
insurance we have, it is again going back to
insurance marketing,
we are not spending this money on any such personal expenses,
okay, so whatever it is, always stay connected with us,
our Ambika's only importance is
not to make a
big software company, GK and those who want to
stay in insurance, thank you, thank you, thank you